Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
I pray You'll be our eyes
And watch us where we go
And help us to be wise
In times where we don't know
Let this be our prayer
When we lose our way
Lead us to a place
Guide us with your grace
To a place where we'll be safe
Kimmy Skota & Jonathan Martinez Performing At The Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
I pray we'll find Your light
And hold it in our hearts
Kimmy Skota & Jonathan Martinez Performing At The Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
When stars go out each night
Let this be our prayer
Kimmy Skota & Jonathan Martinez Performing At The Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
When shadows fill our day
Lead us to a place
Guide us with Your grace
Give us faith so we'll be safe
Kimmy Skota & Jonathan Martinez Performing At The Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
We ask that life be kind
And watch us from above
Kimmy Skota & Jonathan Martinez Performing At The Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
We hope each soul will find
Another soul to love
Let this be our prayer
Just like every child
Needs to find a place
Guide us with Your grace
Give us faith so we'll be safe
Kimmy Skota & Jonathan Martinez Performing At The Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Jonathan Martinez - International Opera Singer
Kimmy Skota - International Opera Singer
God bless you. Thank you.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
The Arrival Of Prophet T.B. Joshua To The Monumental Stadium, Peru Crusade - Day 1
Expectant Crowd Awaits Prophet T.B. Joshua's Arrival To The Peru Crusade - Day 1
Prophet T.B. Joshua At The Monumental Stadium For The Peru Crusade - Day 1
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Glory be to God!
Thank you!
Everything big starts little.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
I can see that prophecy being fulfilled here today.
Let us first recognise our leaders
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
here today
from various areas.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
I salute you.
He who honours a prophet
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
because he is a prophet
receives a prophet's reward.
Thank you for coming.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Our Christian leaders
who have come together to make this revival possible,
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
I salute your faith.
God is our Rewarder.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Thank you.
Thank you once again.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Here I am, your own boy,
without fast legs,
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
smoothness of tongue,
or even ability to inspire people.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
I am here in your presence today.
I say, thank You, Jesus for having designed and created me.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Thank you.
You may be seated, thank you.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Yes, everything big starts little.
Don't forget we were once embryos in our mother's womb.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
See what you have become today.
I want to believe that today is better, tomorrow - best.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Thank You, God!
Every Christian
is a part of Christ's mission.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Jesus told His disciples
in Acts 1
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
what can also be applied to us
that being a missionary
is not an option;
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
it is what we are called to be.
Thank You, Jesus!
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
I want to ask you a question.
What would you do with Jesus
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
as He is still standing on trial?
What would you do with Jesus?
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Ask you neighbour.
What would you do with Jesus,
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
as He is still standing on trial?
If you say that you are a Christian,
are you practising Christianity?
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
What would you do with Jesus?
Don't forget
that to know Jesus Christ
is to know the truth.
Jesus is the truth.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Before we start our message today,
let me get you prepared.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
In order to learn how to serve Jesus in truth and faith,
there are three habits you must learn.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
In order to learn how to serve Jesus in truth,
there are three habits you must learn.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
I call it "habit"
because habit is a gift;
it's a gift of God.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
There are three habits
you must learn.
1. Talk to God every day.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Talk to God every day.
Have you talked to God before coming here today?
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
2. Let God talk to you every day.
If you talk to Him, He must talk to you.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
If you talk to Him in Spirit and truth, He must talk to you.
When you talk to Him and He does not talk to you, it means, you are talking to yourself.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
3. Talk to someone else every day about God.
How many people have you talked to today about Jesus?
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
How many?
Ask your neighbour.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
How many people have you talked to today about Jesus?
He died for you,
He reigns in power for you
and He is still praying for you.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Don't forget.
We live in a two language world.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
One - the language of the Bible
that God uses to heal, bless, create, save, judge, and rule over us.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Two - the everyday language,
the everyday language
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
this is the language that we use to gossip,
the language we use to tell stories,
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
the language we use to do business,
the language we use to play today's politics
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
and the language we use to talk to our children: "Leave the place! Don't be silly!"
Such language cannot be used to talk to God and to talk to someone else about God.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
This is the language we use today.
That is why God cannot hear us.
That is why you cannot hear from God.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
We call it "everyday language"
we use to gossip,
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
to tell stories,
to sing songs,
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
to give directions,
to do business,
to play today's politics.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
That is why after the politics, we may likely not do whatever we promise.
Whatever we promise after the campaign, we may likely not carry it out.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Such language cannot be used to talk to God or to talk to someone else about God.
You cannot use such language to pray: "Jesus! Jesus! Amen! Amen!"
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
You cannot use such language to preach, to teach the Word of God or to counsel.
These are the critical challenges
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
we have in Christiandom today.
This will lead us to "The Integrity Of The Word".
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
So let me take my Bible
The Book of John 6.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
I will quickly take you to the verse 63.
"The Spirit gives life; the flesh counts for nothing.
The Words I have spoken to you - they are full of the Spirit and life."
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Jesus says:
"The Words I spoke to you are Spirit and life".
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Spirit - life.
Don't forget - integrity of the Word.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
This means, the Word is not complete without the Spirit.
This means, the Word is not complete without the Spirit
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
and the Spirit is not complete without the Word.
The Spirit enlightens the Word.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Without the Spirit, the Word will remain inactive.
Without the Spirit, the Word will remain everyday language.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Everyday language is the language we use to gossip, tell stories, sing songs,
to give directions and to do business.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Without the Spirit, the Word will remain everyday language.
That is, without the Spirit, the Word will remain without being.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Oftentimes, it is destructive.
This was what happened to the seven sons of Sceva.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Without the Spirit,
the Word remains idle, lifeless.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
The Spirit lightens the Word.
This is what Jesus meant when He said: "The Words I spoke to you are Spirit and life".
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Without the Spirit, when you say "Jesus", you are talking of yourself
or calling someone who is bearing the name 'Jesus'.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
You know, people bear the name 'Jesus'.
I know many people which say: "My name is Jesus."
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Without the Spirit, when you say "Jesus",
you are calling someone bearing "Jesus" - not Jesus of Nazareth.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
God and His Word are one.
Don't forget, God is Spirit.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
If it is not in the Spirit, it is not in the truth. So, it is all nothing.
I repeat again. God and His Word are one.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Don't forget that God is Spirit.
And His worshippers must worship Him in Spirit and truth.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
If it is not in Spirit, it is not in truth, and so, it is all nothing.
The Word is God speaking to you.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Which means, the Word is the Word of God.
"Thus says Jehovah"
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
is repeated
2,000 times
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
from Exodus to Deuteronomy.
The Word
is always now.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Now!
Before we come to an end of this message,
let's look at the Book of Colossians 3:10.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
"...and have put on the new self which is being renewed in knowledge
in the image of it's Creator."
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
The heart is renewed by studying the Word
and by acting upon the Word.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Take note,
it is not renewed by studying alone but by studying and acting upon the Word.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
One may study the Word of God for years
but if he does not act on it, live by it and practice it,
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
he is not the doer of the Word
and the heart is not renewed.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Going by what we have learned today,
the sick ones can only be healed and delivered
by looking into the Word
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
and by acting upon the Word,
you bring Jesus into the scene
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
to heal,
to deliver,
to bless,
to set free.
Instantly!
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
By looking into the Word and by acting upon the Word,
we bring Jesus into the scene to heal, bless and set free.
Peru Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Thank you.
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 22/06/2018